Guide to the Flute Network Collection 1957-2010 (bulk from 1995-2010)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Flute Network Collection
1957-2010 (bulk from 1995-2010)
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
MS12
Flute Network
24.0 linear feet 23 letter-sized Hollinger boxes, 1 small carton-style box
This collection consists of the working (reference) files for the Flute Network (1957-2010), a non-profit entity that facilitates communication in the flute community.
Catalogues, pamphlets, brochures, flyers, photographs, and CDs in fair condition
Biographical Note
The Flute Network Collection was donated by Jan and Jerry Pritchard and the Flute Network. Founded in 1984 by Jan Spell (later, Jan S. Pritchard), the Flute Network is a non-profit entity, whose purpose is to serve flutists, flute teachers, and the flute community. The overriding purpose of The Flute Network is/was to provide a "bulletin board service" of information pertinent to flutists and flute teachers and to facilitate communications among those interested in the flute. In addition to serving as an information clearing house by phone and mail (before computers were widely used), the Flute Network produced and mailed a publication that went out free of charge, ten times per year, to more than 6,500 different flutists and flute teachers nationwide, as of 2009. With the development and growth of the Internet and the expanded electronic connections between people that came along with that, the Flute Network started a website (www.flutenet.com) and began to share as much of each printed issue as possible through that medium, as well. No membership has ever been required to join the Flute Network. As of February 2013, the print/mail publication remains on planned hiatus, though the website remained active at that time.
The National Flute Association (NFA), founded in 1972, is the largest flute organization in the world. Approximately 6,000 members from more than 50 countries participate in the association, whether in person, online, at conventions, informally and in forums, through publications and classrooms, or in performances. Guided by its goals to encourage a higher standard of artistic excellence for the flute, its performers, and its literature, members include leading soloists, orchestral players, jazz and world music performers, teachers, adult amateurs, and students of all ages (http://www.nfaonline.org/). A quarterly publication is provided to members, and organization membership is required to participate in NFA conventions. The materials from the NFA that are part of this collection were an earned benefit of membership, and were actively used by the Flute Network in performing its services over the years.
This collection consists of the working (reference) files for the Flute Network, including materials donated to the Flute Network History Project. Included in this collection are copies of the Flutist Quarterly as well as membership rosters and pamphlets of the National Flute Association. The materials in this collection were assembled and donated by Jan and Jerry Pritchard of the Flute Network. The donation was facilitated by Hal Ott, Professor of Flute and Music at Central Washington University.
This collection is divided into two series:
I. Flute Advertisements and Publications
II. Miscellaneous, comprising National Flute Association (NFA) Convention booklets, National Flute Association rosters of membership, advertisements for master classes and workshops, programs, newsletters, flute history and photographs, and media consisting of cassettes, compact disks, and diskettes.
Items are organized alphabetically and chronologically within series.
Open to the public for educational research
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Pritchard, Jan S.; Pritchard, Jerry
Flute Network
Flute players; Flutes
Music; Fine Arts
- Flute Advertisements and Publications, I
  - ABA Music (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Abell Woodwinds (Box-folder 1-2)
  - A.D. Geoffrey-Guo (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Alan Handelsman (Box-folder 1-4)
  - Air Power Acoustic Oils (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Alden Lee Company, Inc. (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Alexander Eppler (Box-folder 1-7)
  - Alice Gomez (Box-folder 1-8)
  - All Flutes Plus (Box-folder 1-9)
  - Alphonse Leduc Publications (Box-folder 1-10)
  - ALRY Publications (Box-folder 1-11)
  - Altieri Instrument Bags (Box-folder 1-12)
  - Altus (Box-folder 1-13)
  - American Flute Guild (Box-folder 1-14)
  - Antiqua Publishing (Box-folder 1-15)
  - Anyone Can Whistle (Box-folder 1-16)
  - Applied Microphone Technology (Box-folder 1-17)
  - Apprenti Flutes (Box-folder 1-18)
  - Argentium Sterling Silver (Box-folder 1-19)
  - Arista Flutes (Box-folder 1-20)
  - Armstrong (Box-folder 1-21)
  - Artley (Box-folder 1-22)
  - Bandstand (Box-folder 1-23)
  - Beverly’s Pan Flutes (Box-folder 1-24)
  - ABA Music (Box-folder 1-25)
  - Bill Holcombe’s (Box-folder 1-26)
  - Blocki Pedagogical Flute Products (Box-folder 1-27)
  - Boaz Berney Historical Flutes (Box-folder 1-28)
  - Body Mapping (Box-folder 1-29)
  - Boosey and Hawkes (Box-folder 1-30)
  - Bo-pep, Inc. (Box-folder 1-31)
  - Brannen Brothers (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Breath Builder, Inc. (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Brixton Publications (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Brook Mays Flute Company (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Broude Brothers (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Bulgheroni (Box-folder 2-6)
  - Burkart & Phelan (Box-folder 2-7)
  - Butterfly Headjoints [and Goosman] (Box-folder 2-8)
  - Caliendo Music Publishing (Box-folder 2-9)
  - Cambria Publishing Catalog (Box-folder 2-10)
  - Carolyn Nussbaum Music Company (Box-folder 2-11)
  - Cavallaro Covers (Box-folder 2-12)
  - Carere Music (Box-folder 2-13)
  - Carl Fisher (Box-folder 2-14)
  - C.F. Peters Corporation (Box-folder 2-15)
  - Chen Han Musical Instruments (Box-folder 2-16)
  - Christopher Dwyer Accompaniments (Box-folder 2-17)
  - Cincinnati Flute Works (Box-folder 3-1)
  - Circular Flute (Box-folder 3-2)
  - Clarion (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Clay-Wood-Winds (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Cleanhands (Box-folder 3-5)
  - CMA Publications (Box-folder 3-6)
  - Coda Music Technology (Box-folder 3-7)
  - Concert Design (Box-folder 3-8)
  - Cooperman Fifes (Box-folder 3-9)
  - Cundy-Bettoney Company, Inc. (Box-folder 3-10)
  - Custom Music Company (Box-folder 3-11)
  - Custom Select (Box-folder 3-12)
  - Daniel Deitch (Box-folder 3-13)
  - David Lusk Flutes (Box-folder 3-14)
  - David (and Nina) Shorey Flutes (Box-folder 3-15)
  - David Williams Accompaniments (Box-folder 3-16)
  - David Wimberly Flutes (Box-folder 3-17)
  - Dean Yang Flutes (Box-folder 3-18)
  - Dowani International (Box-folder 3-19)
  - Drelinger (Box-folder 3-20)
  - Drumbeat Indian Arts Inc. (Box-folder 3-21)
  - Durban Cases and Bags (Box-folder 3-22)
  - Dyna Flute System (Box-folder 3-23)
  - e-flutes.com (Box-folder 3-24)
  - E.F. Dean Flutemakers (Box-folder 3-25)
  - E’Lan Flutes (Box-folder 3-26)
  - Educators Music Outlet (Box-folder 3-27)
  - Elliot Weisgarber Associates (Box-folder 3-28)
  - Emmanuel Flutes (Box-folder 3-29)
  - Emerson (Box-folder 3-30)
  - Estudios Marina Marketing (Box-folder 3-31)
  - European American Music Distributors (Box-folder 3-32)
  - Eva Kingma (Box-folder 3-33)
  - Fallen Leaf Press (Box-folder 4-1)
  - Falls House Press (Box-folder 4-2)
  - Ferree’s Tools Inc. (Box-folder 4-3)
  - Finale Music Printing (Box-folder 4-4)
  - Fine Arts Books (Box-folder 4-5)
  - Flutacious (Box-folder 4-6)
  - Flute Center of New York (Box-folder 4-7)
  - Flute Exchange (Box-folder 4-8)
  - Flute Jewelry [various] (Box-folder 4-9)
  - Flutes for the Journey (Box-folder 4-10)
  - Flute Lab (Box-folder 4-11)
  - Flute Parmenon Paris (Box-folder 4-12)
  - Flute Repair Services [various] (Box-folder 4-13)
  - Flute Snake (Box-folder 4-14)
  - Flute Source (Box-folder 4-15)
  - Flute Specialist (Box-folder 4-16)
  - Flute Swab (Box-folder 4-17)
  - Flute World (Box-folder 4-18)
  - Fluteprints (Box-folder 4-19)
  - Folkers and Powell (Box-folder 5-1)
  - Frederic H. Weiner Inc. (1 of 2) (Box-folder 5-2)
  - Frederic H. Weiner Inc. (2 of 2) (Box-folder 5-3)
  - G. Henle Publications (Box-folder 5-4)
  - Gem Headjoints (Box-folder 5-5)
  - Gemeinhardt (Box-folder 5-6)
  - Gemstone Musical Instruments (Box-folder 5-7)
  - Giorgio Flute Headjoints (Box-folder 5-8)
  - Glenn Edward (Box-folder 5-9)
  - Golden River Music (Box-folder 5-10)
  - Great Mind Instruments (Box-folder 5-11)
  - Haggis an’ Neeps Music (Box-folder 5-12)
  - Hall Crystal Flutes (Box-folder 5-13)
  - Hardy’s Musical Instruments (Box-folder 5-14)
  - Harrison-Hurtz Enterprises, Inc. (Box-folder 5-15)
  - Heritage Music (Box-folder 5-16)
  - Howell Roberts Headjoints (Box-folder 5-17)
  - Ian McLauchlan [and Just Flutes] (Box-folder 6-1)
  - IQ Design (Box-folder 6-2)
  - International Music Service (Box-folder 6-3)
  - International Music Suppliers (Box-folder 6-4)
  - International Opus (Box-folder 6-5)
  - International Woodwind, Inc. (Box-folder 6-6)
  - J.B Weissman Music Company (Box-folder 6-7)
  - J.E. Woodwinds (Box-folder 6-8)
  - J.J. Lubrano (Box-folder 6-9)
  - J.L. Smith and Company (Box-folder 7-1)
  - J.R. Lafin (Box-folder 7-2)
  - J.S. Engineering (Box-folder 7-3)
  - Jack Moore Flutes (Box-folder 7-4)
  - Jeanne Inc. (Box-folder 7-5)
  - Jeff Gold Graphics (Box-folder 7-6)
  - Jeffrey Thomas Flute Shop (Box-folder 7-7)
  - John Lehner Flutes Australia (Box-folder 7-8)
  - John Lunn Flutes (Box-folder 7-9)
  - Judi’s Woodwind Shop (Box-folder 7-10)
  - Jung Flutes (Box-folder 7-11)
  - Jupiter Band Instruments (Box-folder 7-12)
  - Katherine Hoover (Box-folder 7-13)
  - Keefe Piccolos (Box-folder 7-14)
  - Kelhorn Corporation (Box-folder 7-15)
  - Kelischek Workshop for Historical Instruments (Box-folder 7-16)
  - Kessler and Sons (Box-folder 7-17)
  - Kori Flutes (Box-folder 7-18)
  - Kotato and Fukushima Flutes (Box-folder 7-19)
  - Lark in the Morning (Box-folder 7-20)
  - Lamberson Flutes (Box-folder 7-21)
  - Landell Flutes (Box-folder 7-22)
  - Last Resort Music Publishing (Box-folder 8-1)
  - LEAF Publishing (Box-folder 8-2)
  - Leblanc Corporation (Box-folder 8-3)
  - Legacy Winds (Box-folder 8-4)
  - Lim’s Crown System (Box-folder 8-5)
  - Little Piper (Box-folder 8-6)
  - Lizzy’s Logos (Box-folder 8-7)
  - Loehr, Groppel, Etcheberry [LGE] (Box-folder 8-8)
  - Lopatin Flute Company (Box-folder 8-9)
  - Lyon and Healy (Box-folder 8-10)
  - Lyric (Box-folder 8-11)
  - M. Baron Company (Box-folder 8-12)
  - Mancke Flutes (Box-folder 8-13)
  - Margun Music Inc. (Box-folder 8-14)
  - Martin Gordon Flutes (Box-folder 8-15)
  - Mateki (Box-folder 8-16)
  - Matit Flutebrothers (Box-folder 8-17)
  - Max Hieber GmbH (Box-folder 8-18)
  - McCanless Flutes (Box-folder 8-19)
  - McGinnis and Marx Music Publications (Box-folder 8-20)
  - McKenna Flutes (Box-folder 8-21)
  - Mel Bay Publications (Box-folder 8-22)
  - Meridian Winds (Box-folder 8-23)
  - Michael J. Allen Flutemaker (Box-folder 8-24)
  - Miyazawa Flutes (Box-folder 9-1)
  - MMB Music Inc. (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Mollenhauer Fulda (Box-folder 9-3)
  - M.S. Jeffries (Box-folder 9-4)
  - M.S.R. Classics (Box-folder 9-5)
  - Muramatsu Flutes (Box-folder 9-6)
  - Muscle Dynamics (Box-folder 9-7)
  - Music Makers Inc. (Box-folder 9-8)
  - Music Makers Inc. (Box-folder 9-9)
  - Music Minus One [MMO] (Box-folder 9-10)
  - Music in Motion (Box-folder 9-11)
  - Music Stand (Box-folder 9-12)
  - Music Treasure Company (Box-folder 9-13)
  - Musically Inclined (Box-folder 9-14)
  - MusiCares (Box-folder 9-15)
  - Musicians Publications (Box-folder 9-16)
  - My Accompanist (Box-folder 9-17)
  - Nagahara Flutes (Box-folder 9-18)
  - Nam Kung Flutes (Box-folder 9-19)
  - NAMM International Music Market (Box-folder 9-20)
  - Native American Flutes (Box-folder 9-21)
  - Native Sounds (Box-folder 9-22)
  - Natsuki Flutes (Box-folder 9-23)
  - Noodle Notes (Box-folder 9-24)
  - Nordt (Box-folder 9-25)
  - Norse Wind Publications (Box-folder 9-26)
  - North East Winds (Box-folder 9-27)
  - Northwind Cases Inc. (Box-folder 9-28)
  - Ogawa Flute (Box-folder 10-1)
  - Olathe Band Instrument (Box-folder 10-2)
  - Old World Flutemakers (Box-folder 10-3)
  - Oleg Products (Box-folder 10-4)
  - One Note Publications (Box-folder 10-5)
  - Pan Publications (Box-folder 10-6)
  - Patrick Olwell Historic Woodwinds (Box-folder 10-7)
  - Pearl Flutes [and Orpheus] (Box-folder 10-8)
  - Petersen Designs (Box-folder 10-9)
  - Phelps Trainer Flutes (Box-folder 10-10)
  - Phillip Hammig (Box-folder 10-11)
  - Power Lung (Box-folder 10-12)
  - Progress Press (Box-folder 10-13)
  - Quick Silver Publications (Box-folder 10-14)
  - Rayburn Musical Instrument Company (Box-folder 10-15)
  - Renditions by Rene (Box-folder 10-16)
  - Rhythmic Medicine (Box-folder 10-17)
  - Roy Seaman Company (Box-folder 10-18)
  - Royalton Music (Box-folder 10-19)
  - Sagerman Flutes (Box-folder 10-20)
  - Sankyo Flutes (Box-folder 10-21)
  - Selmer [and Conn] (Box-folder 10-22)
  - Shakuhachi Flutes (Box-folder 10-23)
  - Sheridan Flute Company (Box-folder 10-24)
  - Simon Polak (Box-folder 10-25)
  - Smart Music Studios (Box-folder 10-26)
  - Sonare (Box-folder 10-27)
  - Sonus Music (Box-folder 10-28)
  - Sound Forth (Box-folder 10-29)
  - Southern Music Company Publishing (Box-folder 10-30)
  - Spautz Fine Furniture (Box-folder 10-31)
  - Spring Flutes (Box-folder 11-1)
  - Stanton’s Sheet Music (Box-folder 11-2)
  - Steglein Publishing, Inc. (Box-folder 11-3)
  - Stranger Creek (Box-folder 11-4)
  - Straubinger Flutes (Box-folder 11-5)
  - Superscope Technologies (Box-folder 11-6)
  - Suzuki (Box-folder 11-7)
  - Swab Cloths [various] (Box-folder 11-8)
  - Sweetheart Flute Company (Box-folder 11-9)
  - Tanzier Piccolo Headjoints (Box-folder 11-10)
  - Tap Music (Box-folder 11-11)
  - Theodore Presser Company (Box-folder 11-12)
  - Thomas Aebi Timber Flutes (Box-folder 11-13)
  - Thumpy the Thumb (Box-folder 11-14)
  - Tolman Woodworking (Box-folder 11-15)
  - Tom Green (Box-folder 11-16)
  - Tom Lacy Flutes (Box-folder 11-17)
  - Tom Marshall-Goetz Instrument Stands (Box-folder 11-18)
  - Tony Bingham (Box-folder 11-19)
  - Tootpick Publishing (Box-folder 11-20)
  - Top Wind (Box-folder 11-21)
  - Trevor J. James (Box-folder 11-22)
  - UMI (Box-folder 12-1)
  - Valgon (Box-folder 12-2)
  - Verlag’s Katalog (Box-folder 12-3)
  - Vivace (Box-folder 12-4)
  - V.Q. Powell (Box-folder 12-5)
  - Volkwein’s Music (Box-folder 12-6)
  - Von Huene Workshop (Box-folder 12-7)
  - Walter Ricke Katalog (Box-folder 12-8)
  - Welan’s Headjoints (Box-folder 12-9)
  - Wesley Flute Company (Box-folder 12-10)
  - Wichita Band Instrument Company (Box-folder 12-11)
  - Williams Flutes (Box-folder 13-1)
  - Wind Player Services (Box-folder 13-2)
  - Wind Song Press Limits (Box-folder 13-3)
  - Wirkkala Designs (Box-folder 13-4)
  - Wiseman Cases (Box-folder 13-5)
  - Wm. S. Haynes (Box-folder 13-6)
  - Woodsong Flutes (Box-folder 13-7)
  - Woodwind Brasswind (Box-folder 13-8)
  - World of Music (Box-folder 13-9)
  - Yamaha (Box-folder 13-10)
  - Zalo-J.P. Publishing (Box-folder 13-11)
- Miscellaneous, II
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1973 (Box-folder 14-1)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1974 (Box-folder 14-2)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1975 (Box-folder 14-3)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1976 (Box-folder 14-4)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1977 (Box-folder 14-5)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1978 (Box-folder 14-6)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1979 (Box-folder 14-7)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1980 (Box-folder 14-8)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1981 (Box-folder 14-9)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1982 (Box-folder 14-10)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1983 (Box-folder 14-11)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1984 (Box-folder 14-12)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1985 (Box-folder 14-13)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1986 (Box-folder 14-14)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1987 (Box-folder 14-15)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1988 (Box-folder 14-16)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1989 (Box-folder 14-17)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1990 (Box-folder 15-1)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1991 (Box-folder 15-2)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1992 (Box-folder 15-3)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1993 (Box-folder 15-4)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1994 (Box-folder 15-5)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1995 (Box-folder 15-6)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1996 (Box-folder 15-7)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1997 (Box-folder 15-8)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1998 (Box-folder 15-9)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 1999 (Box-folder 15-10)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2000 (Box-folder 16-1)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2001 (Box-folder 16-2)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2002 (Box-folder 16-3)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2003 (Box-folder 16-4)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2004 (Box-folder 16-5)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2005 (Box-folder 16-6)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2006 (Box-folder 16-7)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2007 (Box-folder 16-8)
  - National Flute Association Convention Pamphlets, 2008 (Box-folder 16-9)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17-1)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 17-2)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 17-3)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 17-4)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 17-5)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 17-6)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 17-7)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17-8)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 17-9)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17-10)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 18-1)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 18-2)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 18-3)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 18-4)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 18-5)
  - National Flute Association Rosters of Membership, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 18-6)
  - National Flute Association Catalog, 1992 (Box-folder 18-7)
  - National Flute Association, Miscellaneous (Box-folder 18-8)
  - Professional Musicians Directory, 1999 (Box-folder 18-9)
  - Auditions, Competitions and Job Openings (Box-folder 19-1)
  - Conventions and Shows (Box-folder 19-2)
  - Flute Programs (Box-folder 19-3)
  - Institutes (Box-folder 19-4)
  - Master Classes (Box-folder 19-5)
  - Seminars (Box-folder 19-6)
  - Summer Camps (Box-folder 19-7)
  - Summer Retreats (Box-folder 19-8)
  - Summer Schools and Summer Academies (Box-folder 19-9)
  - Symposiums (Box-folder 19-10)
  - Workshops, Courses and Classes (Box-folder 19-11)
  - Concerts, Performances, Recitals, Services, Events (Box-folder 20-1)
  - Fairs (Box-folder 20-2)
  - Festivals (Box-folder 20-3)
  - Flute Magazines (Box-folder 20-4)
  - Flute Articles (Box-folder 20-5)
  - New Releases [Books, CDs, Music, etc] (Box-folder 20-6)
  - Request to Join Various Clubs or Organizations (Box-folder 20-7)
  - Scholarships (Box-folder 20-8)
  - Newsletter--Burkart Flutes and Piccolos (Box-folder 21-1)
  - Newsletter--COFA [Central Ohio Flute Association] (Box-folder 21-2)
  - Newsletter--Connections (Box-folder 21-3)
  - Newsletter--Florida Flute Association (Box-folder 21-4)
  - Newsletter--Flute Forum (Box-folder 21-5)
  - Newsletter--Flute Sounds (Box-folder 21-6)
  - Newsletter--Flutemaker (Box-folder 21-7)
  - Newsletter--Hands On (Box-folder 21-8)
  - Newsletter--Houston Flute Flub (Box-folder 21-9)
  - Newsletter--Key Notes (Box-folder 21-10)
  - Newsletter--Lombardo Music Publications (Box-folder 21-11)
  - Newsletter--Notes – Selmer Woodwind (Box-folder 21-12)
  - Newsletter--Red Chamber Music (Box-folder 21-13)
  - Newsletter--Seminar Newsletter – Eleanor Lawrence (Box-folder 21-14)
  - Newsletter--Traverso – Baroque Flute Newsletter (Box-folder 21-15)
  - Newsletter--Verne Q. Powell Flutes (Box-folder 21-16)
  - Newsletter--Washington Flute Scene (Box-folder 21-17)
  - Newsletter--Yamaha Backstage Pass (Box-folder 21-18)
  - Newsletters--Miscellaneous (Box-folder 21-19)
  - Book--The Flute through the Ages (Box-folder 22-1)
  - Flute History Project (Box-folder 22-2)
  - Historical articles (Box-folder 22-3)
  - Historical articles (Box-folder 22-4)
  - Historical articles (Box-folder 22-5)
  - Historical reference material (Box-folder 22-6)
  - Paper--“The Development of the Flute” (Box-folder 22-7)
  - Photographs, [various] (Box-folder 22-8)
  - Printed emails, correspondence, notes (Box-folder 22-9)
  - CD--“The Brannen-Cooper Kingma System Flute with Robert Dick” (Box-folder 23-1)
  - CD--Lopatin Flute Company presents “Dreams to Reality” (Box-folder 23-2)
  - CD--Lopatin presents “Squarely in the Holiday Spirit” (Box-folder 23-3)
  - CD--Louis Lewis, “Kristin’s Story” (Box-folder 23-4)
  - CD--“Matti Helin plays the Carbon Fibre Flute” (Box-folder 23-5)
  - CD--MSR, “Flute Sampler”, Summer 2006 (Box-folder 23-6)
  - CD--“Play Along with Paul Edmund-Davies” (Box-folder 23-7)
  - CD--“Power Lung” (Box-folder 23-8)
  - CD--“Selmer 1.0” (Box-folder 23-9)
  - Cassette--Unlabeled (Box-folder 23-10)
  - Diskette--Flute Master Classes, NFA List, 1997 (Box-folder 23-11)